# TRUONG NGUYEN

Full Stack Software Engineer +61490493625

anhtruong.works@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/at-dev/ https://t-folio.vercel.app/ https://github.com/anhtruong-it

As a final year student at Griffith University and a passionate software developer, I have two years of experience in building web applications of varying complexities. I am a strong supporter of continuous improvement and strive to create a structured code base and improved development processes in all projects. My belief in clean code guides my work and helps me create applications that are both efficient and effective.

My goal is to continuously improve my technical skills and make a positive impact on people's lives through my work. I am dedicated to enhancing my crafting skills and creating solutions that are not only functional but impactful.

### **EXPERIENCES**

SeaWorld Australia Feb 2023 – Jun 2023

Software Engineer

- Build and implement a game interface controlled by Raspberry Pi controller. Purpose of creating activities to enrich dolphins.
- Languages & Technologies: Python, Embedded system, Raspberry Pi controller.

Jung Talents Nov 2021 – Dec 2022

Software Engineer

## https://www.mentem.co/

- Built and managed APIs backend application on Docker with NestJS, and GraphQL.
- Developing front-end GUI on an education website with NextJS, Auth0, code review.
- Researching and writing documentations in Confluence.

# https://www.cclmagic.com.au/

- Continuously refined the old database from MongoDB server to refactoring database and deploy to a S3 AWS service.
- Found solutions for website domain name by using google domain health check.

#### **PROJECTS**

## • Chat System (2022, Font-end):

- Build a web app that lets people chat. Chat system including Super-Admin, Admin, Support and Users. Each object can chat with each other in a certain chat channel in real time through building server and front end.
- Languages & Technologies: JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML/CSS, MongoDB, Docker, Socket, REST API, Angular.

## • Airbnb Data Sydney (2021, Data analyst):

- Airbnb Sydney's data statistics software where users can look up hotels, houses in Sydney, hotel prices, amenities, customer reviews, compare prices between two areas. Given data are excel files from Airbnb (2019).

- Languages & Technologies: Python, SQLite, Pandas, Matplotlib, Data.csv.

## • Car Booking Website (2021, Back-end):

- Build a web app based on a dynamic database, where users can view vehicle information, make reservations, cancel schedules, CRUD for users and vehicles.
- Languages & Technologies: SQL, PHP, Laravel, HTML/CSS.

## • Pacman (2021):

- Pacman game implemented in Python (group work 3 people).
- Languages & Technologies: Python, Unit tests.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Software Engineering**

## **Griffith University**

**2021 – Present** 

• Core coursework: Data Analysis & OOP: Python, SQLite; Backend development: PHP & Laravel framework; Full stack development: Node.js, JavaScript & Angular framework; IOS: Swift. GPA: 5.6

# **Diploma of Engineering**

## **Griffith College**

2019 - 2020

• Core coursework: Introducing to C and MATLAB, Statistics, Calculus, Fundamental of engineering, Project management. GPA: 6.2

### HONORS AND AWARDS

• Academic Excellence: Graduated Diploma of Engineering

2020

• Academic Excellence: Software Engineering – Griffith University

2021

## **TECHNOLOGIES SKILLS**

- Programming Languages: Competent in Python, Javascript, Typescript, C#.
- Database: SQL, MongoDB, DynamoDB.
- Frameworks: Angular, React, NextJS, NodeJS, .NET, NestJS, Flask.
- Development Tools and Other Technologies: Git, VS Code, PyCharm, Docker, Kubernetes, AWS, Agile Development, GraphQL.
- Architectures: Microservice, Serverless.

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Problem-solving.
- Critical thinking.
- Willing to learn newer techniques.
- Passion for learning and working.
- Teamwork.
- Documentation.
- Code review.